<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-05-08T15:39:17-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">MM</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><author><name>First Lastname</name></author><entry><title type="html">Why are we creating this organization?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/why-create/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why are we creating this organization?" /><published>2020-05-08T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-05-08T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/why-create</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/why-create/">&lt;p&gt;This is a personal question for each member in our organization, but let me attempt to answer with my own motivation. I know that I am
who I am today only because of the people who have helped shape and guide me over many years and through many hours of mentorship. In these
scary times I find myself often thinking of all those people. Thinking about my wife, Kaitlin, who is a nurse practitioner out there making sure 
kids are getting the care they need. I am humbled thinking of all the practical help she provides to so many people. I think about my old PhD advisors 
Dr. Michael Raymer and Dr. Travis Doom (cool name right?). I feel like I randomly found their lab during my last year in college. 
It wasn’t completely random though. They like so many people around the world were trying to do good way before there was a pandemic. 
They were trying to pursue applied research for all the right reasons, but more than that they were drawn to education because
of the good they could do for others. For me, this group and organization is a way for me to try to do some good. To be one of the helpers. And
if that last phrase rings a bell you either have a great memory or you have young children like I do. I pulled it from the one and only Mr. Rogers 
who once said:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;When I was a boy and I would see scary things in the news, my mother would say to me,&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;blockquote&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Look for the helpers. You will always find people who are helping.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paul Anderson, Ph.D.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>First Lastname</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><category term="update" /><summary type="html">This is a personal question for each member in our organization, but let me attempt to answer with my own motivation. I know that I am who I am today only because of the people who have helped shape and guide me over many years and through many hours of mentorship. In these scary times I find myself often thinking of all those people. Thinking about my wife, Kaitlin, who is a nurse practitioner out there making sure kids are getting the care they need. I am humbled thinking of all the practical help she provides to so many people. I think about my old PhD advisors Dr. Michael Raymer and Dr. Travis Doom (cool name right?). I feel like I randomly found their lab during my last year in college. It wasn’t completely random though. They like so many people around the world were trying to do good way before there was a pandemic. They were trying to pursue applied research for all the right reasons, but more than that they were drawn to education because of the good they could do for others. For me, this group and organization is a way for me to try to do some good. To be one of the helpers. And if that last phrase rings a bell you either have a great memory or you have young children like I do. I pulled it from the one and only Mr. Rogers who once said:</summary></entry></feed>